{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Ductwork Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40419/":{"taskOID":40419,"originalTaskOID":40419,"setID":711,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6943,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Ductwork Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of the ductwork project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10169,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install new ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Install new ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10170,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace existing ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10171,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6944,"questionDisplayText":"Type of System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of system is the ductwork for? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10172,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Gas-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10173,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electric-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Electric-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10174,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Oil-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10175,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood/pellet stove","answerDisplayText":"Wood/pellet stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10176,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10177,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Air conditioner","answerDisplayText":"Air conditioner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10178,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6945,"questionDisplayText":"Number of rooms/areas needing registers","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms/areas need registers?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10179,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10180,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 5","answerDisplayText":"2 - 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10181,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 10","answerDisplayText":"6 - 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10182,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11 - 15","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10183,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 15","answerDisplayText":"More than 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10184,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6943,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Ductwork Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of the ductwork project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10169,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install new ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Install new ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10170,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace existing ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10171,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10169,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install new ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Install new ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10170,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace existing ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10171,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6944,"questionDisplayText":"Type of System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of system is the ductwork for? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10172,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Gas-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10173,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electric-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Electric-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10174,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Oil-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10175,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood/pellet stove","answerDisplayText":"Wood/pellet stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10176,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10177,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Air conditioner","answerDisplayText":"Air conditioner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10178,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10172,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Gas-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10173,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electric-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Electric-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10174,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Oil-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10175,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood/pellet stove","answerDisplayText":"Wood/pellet stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10176,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10177,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Air conditioner","answerDisplayText":"Air conditioner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10178,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6945,"questionDisplayText":"Number of rooms/areas needing registers","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms/areas need registers?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10179,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10180,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 5","answerDisplayText":"2 - 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10181,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 10","answerDisplayText":"6 - 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10182,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11 - 15","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10183,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 15","answerDisplayText":"More than 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10184,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10179,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10180,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 5","answerDisplayText":"2 - 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10181,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 10","answerDisplayText":"6 - 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10182,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11 - 15","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10183,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 15","answerDisplayText":"More than 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10184,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40419/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40419,"taskName":"Ducts \u0026 Vents - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Ductwork","xmTaskDescriptor":"Ductwork Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":63,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Airconditioning Ducts Ductwork AC air","textMessagingName":"Install Duct Work","rolloverLongDesc":"These specialists have the tools \u0026 equipment to fold \u0026 shape metal to form duct work.  They are also equipped to determine the best way to route the ducts through a building \u0026 may also handle the construction of any bulkheads needed to hide duct work in finished spaces.  Note separate categories for sheet-metal fabricators \u0026 metal roofing.","rolloverShortDesc":"Metal air tubes used for heating \u0026 air conditioning.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Ductwork.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Ductwork Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Duct \u0026 Vent Installation Services","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":39,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Ducts \u0026 Vents Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Ducts \u0026 Vents - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Duct and Vent Project","urlName":"Ducts-Vents-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Duct \u0026 Vent Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"ducts, vents, ductwork,","emcCategoryOid":-12040,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":711,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}